你们看 丑裸男在收拾东西
Oh, hey, you guys, look. Ugly Naked Guy's putting stuff in boxes.
噢
Oh.
看样子我们的裸友要搬家了
Huh. I'd say from the looks of it, our naked buddy is moving.
讽刺的是大部分的箱子 都标示着"衣服"
Ironically, most of the boxes seem to be labeled "Clothes."
我会怀念那个大屁股的
Aw, I'm going to miss that big old squishy butt.
鸡肉炒饭吃不下了
And we're done with the chicken fried rice.
嘿 如果他要搬走 我可以去把那里租下来
Hey. Hey, if he's moving, maybe I should try to get his place.
- 对啊   - 好主意
- Oh, yeah.      - Good idea.
跟你们遥遥相对多好玩啊
It would be so cool to live across from you guys.
那我们就可以玩电话游戏
Yeah, hey, then we could do that telephone thing...
你一个罐子 我们一个罐子
...you know, where you have a can, we have a can...
中间有一条线
...and it's connected by a string.
或者我们也可以打真的电话
Or we could do the actual telephone thing.
天哪 我爱死这间公寓了
Oh, my God. I love this apartment.
很完美吧？
Isn't it perfect?
我居然没发现这里有这么棒
I can't believe I never realized how great it is.
因为你的目光会马上移到丑裸男身上
That is because your eye immediately goes to the big naked man.
太棒了
It's amazing.
你最好赶快去申请 否则我会抢先
You better hurry up and fill out an application, or I'll beat you to it.
哦 呵呵
Oh, heh.
没想到会有这一天 我要去用丑裸男的厕所了
Well, I never thought I'd say this, but I'm gonna go use Ugly Naked Guy's bathroom.
你看 是摩妮卡和钱德 喂
Oh, look. There's Monica and Chandler. Hey!
喂 你们好 喂
Hey, you guys! Hey!
噢
Oh!
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
钱德和摩妮卡 钱德和摩妮卡
Aah! Chandler and Monica. Chandler and Monica.
天哪
Oh, my God.
- 钱德和摩妮卡   - 天哪
- Chandler and Monica!     - Oh, my God!
我要瞎了 我要瞎了
Oh, my eyes! My eyes!
- 菲比 菲比   - 喔
- Phoebe. Phoebe.     - OW!
没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
- 不 他们搞在一起   - 我知道
- No, they're doing it!     - I know.
- 我知道   - 你知道？
- I know. I know.     - You know?
对 我知道 乔伊也知道 但罗斯不知道
Yes, I know, and Joey knows, but Ross doesn't...
所以你别再叫了
...so you have to stop screaming!
怎么了？
Hey, what's going on?
- 怎么了？ - 没事
- What?     - Nothing.
我们只是好兴奋你要搬来这里
Oh, God, we're just so excited that you might get this apartment.
- 这里的确很棒   - 很棒
- Actually, it looks really good.     - Aah! It looks pretty good!
快过来啊
Get in here! Come on!
(中央咖啡厅)
你是说每次摩妮卡和钱德…
You mean whenever Monica and Chandler were, like...
去洗衣服或买东西？
...doing laundry or going grocery shopping...?
她每次跟伤心的琳达讲电话？
All that time Monica spent on the phone with sad Linda from camp?
嘿咻 嘿咻 色情电话
Uh-huh. Doing it, doing it, phone doing it.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
真是太好了… 对男方来说
I mean, I think it's great. For him.
女方可以有更好的对象
She might be able to do better.
- 你们好   - 乔伊 快过来
- Hey, you guys.     - Joey, come here. Come here.
菲比发现摩妮卡和钱德的事了
Phoebe just found out about Monica and Chandler.
就是他们是朋友 如此而已？
You mean how they're friends and nothing more?
不 乔伊 她知道了
No. No, Joey, she knows.
我们刚才在丑裸男的公寓 看到他们隔着窗户在做
We were at Ugly Naked Guy's apartment and saw them doing it through the window.
应该说是靠着窗户在做
Actually, we saw them doing it up against the window.
他们知道你知道 但是不知道瑞秋知道？
Okay, so now they know you know, and they don't know Rachel knows?
对 但现在这些都不重要了
Yes, but you know what? It doesn't matter who knows what.
我们有三个人知道 就可以告诉他们了
Now enough of us know that we could just tell them we know.
我再也不必说谎保密了
Now all the lying and the secrets will finally be over.
或者我们也可以不告诉他们 自己来找点乐子
Or we could not tell them we know and have a little fun of our own.
什么意思？
Well, what do you mean?
譬如每次他们说要洗衣服
You know, every time they say they're doing laundry...
我们就给他们一堆衣服洗
...we'll give them laundry to do.
- 我喜欢   - 不…
- Oh, I would enjoy that.     - No, no, no.
你知道怎样更好玩？告诉他们
Wait, Rach, you know what would be even more fun? Telling them.
- 不 我想照菲比的做法   - 我没办法再…
- Yeah, no, I want to do Phoebe's thing.     - I can't take any...
你只要别说我们知道就行了
You don't have to do anything. Just don't tell them that we know.
不要 我没办法再保密了
No. I can't take any more secrets.
我有你们的秘密 他们的秘密 还有我自己的秘密
I got your secrets, I got their secrets. I got secrets of my own, you know.
- 你才没有秘密   - 是吗？
- You don't have any secrets.     - Oh, yeah?
你就不知道 我有个企鹅抱枕叫抱宝
Well, you don't know about Hugsy, my bedtime penguin pal.
所以…
So, ahem, um ....
我们要怎么耍他们？
How are we going to mess with them?
你可以利用室友的身分
Well, you could use your position as the roommate.
我就运用我最大的本钱
And then I would use, you know, the strongest tool at my disposal.
我的性感
My sexuality.
- 孩子们   - 嘿
- Hello, children.     - Hey.
仔细看 学着点 别吃我的饼干
Okay. Watch, learn, and don't eat my cookie.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你穿这件外套真好看
Ooh. Wow, that jacket looks great on you.
- 是吗？ - 对 这个料子摸起来好软
- Really?     - Yeah. The material looks so soft.
你好啊 二头肌先生
Oh, hello, Mr. Bicep.
你有在健身吗？
You've been working out?
我有在挤牙膏
Well, I try to, you know, squeeze things.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
如果你真的想知道…
Well, if you really wanna know...
我不能告诉你
Oh, I can't tell you this.
菲比 你什么都可以告诉我
Phoebe, it's me, you can tell me anything.
事实上我就是不能告诉你
Well, actually, you're the one person I can't tell this to.
但我又最想告诉你
And the one person I want to the most.
怎么了？
What's going on?
因为我很久没跟男人在一起了
I think it's just, you know, that I haven't been with a guy in so long...
有时你一直寻寻觅觅
...and you know how sometimes you're looking for something...
却没发现他就在你眼前喝咖啡
...and you don't see that it's right there in front of you, sipping coffee ....
我说太多了吗？
Oh, no. Have I said too much?
总之你考虑一下 我就会考虑
Well, just something to think about. I know I will.
喔 哈哈
Ooh. Ha, ha.
- 你好可爱   - 呵
- You are so cute.     - Heh.
你怎么会这么可爱？
How did you get to be so cute?
我爷爷是瑞典人
Well, my grandfather was Swedish.
我奶奶其实是只拇指兔
And my grandmother was actually a tiny little bunny.
你变得更可爱了
Okay, now you're even cuter.
这简直是今天的民意
You know, that is a popular opinion today, I must say.
什么？
What?
今天在咖啡厅发生了件怪事
The weirdest thing happened at the Coffeehouse.
我觉得菲比在钓我
I think Phoebe was hitting on me.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
是真的 菲比觉得我很有魅力
I'm telling you, I think Phoebe thinks I'm foxy.
- 不可能   - 喔
- It's not possible.     - Ow.
抱歉 只是在菲比眼中
I'm sorry, it's just Phoebe's just always thought you were charming...
你的迷人是无性的
...in a sexless kind of way.
这种话真是百听不厌
Oh, well, you know, I can't hear that enough.
抱歉 你应该误解她的意思了
I'm sorry, I just think you misunderstood her.
我没有误解 好吗？她只差没扑上来
No, I didn't misunderstand, okay? She was all over me.
她还摸我的二头肌呢
She touched my bicep, for crying out loud.
这块二头肌？
This bicep?
是我现在没挤它
Well, it's not flexed right now.
摩妮卡 你要干什么？要不要一起去看电影？
Hey, Mon, what are you doing? Want to come see a movie with us?
事实上我正要去洗衣服
Uh, actually, I was going to do some laundry.
- 钱德 要不要起去？ - 好啊 我跟你起去
- Chandler, you want to do it with me?     - Sure, I'll do it with you.
太好了 等一下
Okay, great. Hold on a second.
拿去
Unh. Here you go.
不介意吧？这样我就轻松多了
You don't mind, do you? That would really help me out a lot. Thanks.
我的硬币应该不够
Ha, ha. You know what? I don't think I have enough quarters.
我这里有
Oh, I have quarters.
- 嘿   - 罗斯 公寓申请得怎样？
- Hey.      - Hey, Ross, any word on the apartment yet?
我打过去问 原来丑裸男要自己转租
Well, I called over there, and it turns out Ugly Naked Guy is subletting it himself.
而且已经有一大堆申请者
And he's already had like 100 applicants.
总之差别是我占了优势
Oh.No, no, I've got the edge.
我知道这样有点奸诈 但我送了点东西…
I know it's not exactly ethical, but I sent him a bribe...
去贿赂他
...to tip the scales in my direction.
从窗户搞不好看得到
Yeah. Check it out, you can see it from the window.
是那个打了蝴蝶结的弹珠台吗？
Oh, is it that pinball machine with the big bow on it?
不是
No.
那辆新的登山车？
That new mountain bike?
不是
No.
那你送什么？
Well, what did you send?
一篮小英式松饼
A basket of mini muffins.
但桌上全都是小英式松饼
There's a whole table of mini muffin baskets.
哪一篮是你送的？
Which one did you send?
小的那一篮
The small one.
什么？你真以为那篮松饼能帮你争取到公寓？
What? You actually thought that basket was gonna get you the apartment?
对
Well, yeah.
我们办公室曾经收到一篮 大家都爱得不得了
Someone sent us a basket at work once and people went crazy over those muffins.
那天真的很高兴
It was the best day.
你的工作让我觉得好悲惨
Your work makes me sad.
真是的 我好想要那间公寓
Oh, man, I want that place so much.
我还以为一定会成功
And I was so sure that was going to work.
那12块算是丢到水里了
There's 12 bucks I'll never see again.
好了 想看电影就得快了
All right, we'd better go if we're gonna catch that movie.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Bye.
钱德再见 我已经开始想你了
Bye, Chandler. I miss you already.
你看到她唠哩唠气还捏我吗？
Okay, did you see that? With the inappropriate, and the pinching?
我看到了
Actually, I did.
你相信她对我有意思了吧？
So now do you believe that she's attracted to me?
天哪… 她知道我们的事了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. She knows about us.
真的还假的？
Are you serious?
菲比知道了 她想吓我们
Phoebe knows, and she's just trying to freak us out.
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation for it.
那我好捏的屁股和激凸的二头肌呢？
Okay, but what about my pinchable butt and my bulging biceps?
她知道了
She knows.
乔伊
Joey.
怎样？
Yeah?
菲比知道我们的事了
Phoebe knows about us.
我没告诉她们
Well, I didn't tell them.
她们？她们是谁？
Them? Who's "them"?
菲比和乔伊
Uh, Phoebe and Joey.
乔伊
Joey.
和瑞秋
And Rachel.
我想告诉你们 但她们逼我不能说
Look, I would have told you, but they made me promise not to tell.
- 天哪   - 对不起
- Oh, man.     - I'm sorry.
那现在没事了吧？
But, hey, it's over now, right?
你们可以告诉她们你们知道了
Because you can tell them you know they know...
我就可以恢后我状况外的本色
...and I can go back to knowing absolutely nothing.
- 除非…   - 没有除非 现在就要了结
- Unless...     - No, not "unless." This must end now.
她们还自以为高明
Oh, man, they think they are so slick messing with us.
她们不知道我们知道她们知道
But they don't know that we know that they know.
- 所以   - 没错
- Son     - Ah, yes.
耍人的变成被耍的
The messers become the messees.
罗斯 别再折磨自己了
Oh, Ross, honey, you gotta stop torturing yourself.
你去找别的公寓嘛
Why don't you just find another apartment?
我这个月已经看了上千间公寓
I've already looked at like a thousand apartments this month.
没有一间比得上那一间
None of them even compares to that one.
你知道你应该怎么做？
You know what you should do?
你应该找出他的嗜好 拿来跟他套交情
You should find out what his hobbies are and then use that to bond with him.
例如我对乔伊有所求
Yeah. Like if I wanted something from Joey...
我就会聊… 三明治
...I would strike up a conversation about, say, um, sandwiches...
或是我的内衣
...or, uh, my underwear.
我在听
I'm listening.
看吧
See?
好棒的主意
That is a great idea.
而且我了解丑裸男 因为我们偷窥了他5年
And I know Ugly Naked Guy because we've been watching him for five years.
所以我又重新占了上风
So that gives me back my edge. Ha, ha.
好 他有一张跳床
Let's see now. He had the trampoline.
- 被他跳坏了   - 他有双倒吊鞋
- But he broke that.     - Well, he had gravity boots.
也被他穿坏了
Yeah, he broke those too.
所以他喜欢破坏东西
So he likes to break stuff.
好 我得去接小班 不过我会想出来的
Okay, I've got to go pick up Ben, but I will figure something out.
他之前不是有一只猫？
Hey, didn't he used to have a cat?
别提那个 会害他心情不好
I wouldn't bring that up. It would probably just bum him out.
可怜的猫咪 没看到大屁股压下来
Poor cat never saw that big butt coming.
喂？
Hello?
在 等一下 她就在旁边
Oh, yeah, hey. Hold on a second, she's right here.
钱德找你
it's Chandler.
哦
Oh.
你好
Hello, you.
菲比 我一整天都在想你
Hello, Phoebe, I've been thinking about you all day.
啊？
Huh?
你之前的提议 说我不心动是骗人的
Well, you know that thing you said before? I'd be lying if I said I wasn't intrigued.
是吗？
Really?
对 乔伊晚上不在
Yeah. Listen, Joey won't be here tonight.
你要不要过来 我让你摸我的二头肌
Why don't you come over and I'll let you, uh, feel my bicep.
甚至是别的地方
Or maybe more.
我待会再给你答复 再见
I'll have to get back to you on that. Okay, bye.
天哪 他找我去摸他的二头肌和别的地方
Oh, my God. He wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more.
- 不会吧？ - 是真的
- Are you kidding?     - No.
他居然背着摩妮卡…
I cannot believe he would do that to Mon...
乔伊 他们知道我们知道吗？
Joey? Do they know that we know?
- 不知道   - 乔伊？
- No.     - Joey?
- 他们知道你们知道了   - 我就知道
- They know you know.     - Ooh, I knew it.
那两个人真扯
Oh, I cannot believe those two.
他们以为他们可以耍我们？想耍我们是吧？
They thought they could mess with us? They're trying to mess with us?
他们不知道我们知道 他们知道我们知道了
They don't know that we know they know we know.
乔伊 你不能说
And, Joey, you can't say anything.
我也不想说了
Couldn't if I wanted to.
你好 我是罗斯盖勒
Good evening, sir. My name is Ross Geller.
我也申请要租你的公寓
I'm one of the people who applied for the apartment...
我知道竞争很激烈 但是…
...and I realize that the competition is fierce, but ....
抱歉 我注意到你光着身体
I'm sorry, I can't help but notice that you're naked and ....
我为你鼓掌
I applaud you.
我也好想光着身体
Man, I wish I was naked.
看起来好舒服
I mean, this looks so great.
这正是上帝造人的本意
That is how God intended it.
- 你看她们多慌   - 她们绝对会退缩
- Look at them. They're panicked.     - Oh, yeah, they're totally gonna back down.
没错
Oh, yeah.
好 他敢约我就敢去
All right, if he wants a date, he's going to get a date.
- 我要过去了   - 好
- I'm going to go in.     - Okay, okay.
性感一点
Be sexy.
拜托
Please.
钱德 我晚上可以过去
So, Chandler, I'd love to come by tonight.
真的？
Really?
当然 就7点吧？
Oh, absolutely. Should we say around 7?
好
Yes.
很好 我很期待跟你发生性关系
Good. I'm really looking forward to you and me having sexual intercourse.
快来看 丑裸男有裸友来访
Hey, hey, check it out, check it out. Ugly Naked Guy's got a naked friend.
真的
Oh, yeah.
天哪 那是我们的朋友
Oh, my God. That's our friend.
- 是裸罗斯   - 是罗斯
- it's Naked Ross.     - It is Ross!
上场罗
Showtime.
瑞秋 拿香水来
Okay, Rachel, get me perfume.
乔伊 帮我拿一瓶酒和两个酒杯
And, Joey, can you get me a bottle of wine and glasses?
放心好了
All right, it'll be great.
只要让她以为你想跟她上床 她绝对会吓到
You just make her think you want to have sex with her and it'll freak her out.
我到底得撑到什么程度？
Okay, listen, how far am I gonna have to go with her?
别紧张 她会比你先投降
Relax, she's gonna give in way before you do.
- 你怎么知道？ - 因为你跟我同队
- How do you know?     - Because you're on my team.
我这一队总是赢
And my team always wins.
赢这种事？
At this?
总之去吓她 快去
Just go get some. Go.
好 我会站在门外听
Okay, honey, now, I'm gonna try to listen from right here.
- 好   - 等下
- Okay.      - Okay. Oh, wait.
- 好主意   - 等等
- Good idea.     - Yeah.
- 别把料都爆光了   - 好
- Don't give away the farm.     - Okay.
菲比
Phoebe.
- 钱德   - 进来吧
- Chandler.     - Come on in.
我正要进去
I was going to.
我带了酒来 你要吗？
Um, I brought some wine. Would you like some?
好啊
Sure.
总算要开始了 紧张吗？
So here we are. Nervous?
我？不会 你呢？
Me? No. You?
不会 这样正合我意
No. I want this to happen.
我也是
So do I.
我去放点音乐
I'm going to put on some music.
那我… 我跳舞给你看好了
Maybe... Maybe I'll dance for you.
你真美
You look good.
谢谢
Thanks. Heh.
你说这种话让我好想…
You know, when you say things like that, it makes me wanna...
扯掉你的毛衣背心
...rip that sweater vest right off.
不如进房里再说吧？
Well, why don't we move this into the bedroom?
- 真的吗？ - 你不想吗？
- Really?     - Oh, do you not want to?
不是
No. No.
只是我想先脱掉衣服
I just, you know, first, I wanna take off all my clothes...
让你替我擦乳液
...and have you rub lotion on me.
听起来不错
Well, that would be nice.
我去拿乳液
I'll go get the lotion.
情况完全失控了 她要我帮她擦乳液
This is totally getting out of hand, okay? She wants me to put lotion on her.
- 她在唬你   - 她没打算放弃
- She's bluffing.     - Look, she's not backing down.
她还这样
She went like this...
他没打算放弃 他去拿乳液了
He's not backing down. He went to get lotion.
真是的 你们还没好吗？
Oh, man, aren't you guys done yet?
我想坐我的椅子
I want to sit in my chair.
乔伊 菲比一突破钱德的心防
Joey, look at it this way, the sooner Phoebe breaks Chandler...
这一切就结束公开了
...the sooner this is all over and out in the open.
我喜欢
Ooh, I like that.
我知道 让他看你的胸罩 他怕胸罩 他解不开
Oh, okay. Show him your bra. He's afraid of bras. Can't work them.
乔伊
Joey!
你没把扣子都挑开
Wow, you didn't rip off any buttons.
老经验了
It's not my first time.
你给我回去 色诱她让她屈服
You go back out there and you seduce her till she cracks.
好 等一下
Okay. Give me a second.
- 你打扫过吗？ - 当然罗
- Did you clean up in here?     - Of course.
你… 要走了？
Oh, you're, uh... You're going?
除非你跟我走 爱人
Um, not without you, lover.
这是我的胸罩
So this is my bra.
很好看
It's very, very nice.
过来
Well, come here.
我很高兴我们要做爱了
I'm very happy we're gonna have all the sex.
你是该高兴 我的身体很柔软
You should be. I'm very bendy.
- 我要吻你了   - 除非我先吻你
- I'm gonna kiss you now.     - Not if I kiss you first.
接下来就只能接吻了
Well, I guess there's nothing left for us to do but kiss.
终于来了
Here it comes.
我们的初吻
Our first kiss.
好… 你赢了
Okay, okay, okay. You win.
- 哈   - 我不能跟你上床
- Ha!     - I can't have sex with you.
- 为什么？ - 因为我爱摩妮卡
- And why not?     - Because I'm in love with Monica.
你什么？
You're... You're what?
爱她 没错 我爱她
Love her. That's right. I love her.
我爱她
I love her.
我爱你 摩妮卡
I love you, Monica.
我也爱你 钱德
I love you too, Chandler.
我以为你们只是搞在一起 我不知道你们相爱
I just thought you guys were doing it. I didn't know you were in love.
兄弟
Dude.
向菲比致敬 强劲的对手
Hats off to Phoebe. Quite a competitor.
此外你的胸部还晾在外面
And may I say your breasts are still showing?
天哪
God.
好耶 就这样
All right. So that's it?
结束了 大家都知道了
It's over. Everybody knows.
罗斯还不知道
Well, actually, Ross doesn't.
对 请你们先别告诉他
Yes, and we'd appreciate it if no one told him yet.
就是这里 新罗斯的新家
A new place for a new Ross.
我一布置好…
I'm gonna have you and all the guys from work over...
就请你和同事来坐
...once it's, you know, furnished.
很高兴看到你重新振作
I must say, it's nice to see you back on your feet.
我是振作了 脾气暴躁的事都过去了
Well, I am that, uh, and the whole rage thing is definitely behind me.
你是不是该回馆里上班了？
I wonder if it's time for you to rejoin our team at the museum.
唐诺 那就太好了
Oh, Donald, that would be great.
我已经准备好重回岗位 我…
I am totally ready to come back to work.
什么？不
What? No.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
别压着我妹妹
Get off my sister!